can tadalafil be used for women and if
so what are the benefits and is this
another dose than for
men sure um women have erections no
different than men do they just have
slightly different uh Anatomy but uh if
you look at the in the fetal State prior
to development in the womb uh men and
women are identical and the female
anatomy simply develops differently into
a male you know prior to birth
so women have erections no different
than men it's nothing more than an
increase in blood flow to the region it
can heighten sensitivity it can heighten
arousal and uh it works in the same
fashion via the same mechanism via the
inhibition of the phosphatase 5
enzyme dose I would tell women generally
speaking most women tend to be slightly
smaller than men as a whole in in terms
of body mass I would say start at a
smaller dose and if it works for you
great and if it doesn't then increase
men like to use generally 5 milligram a
day as as a base some men develop some
side effects like pumps or cramps in the
lower back upper legs uh hamstring area
some develop some heartburn we tell
these guys usually to either try in
every other day Administration or cut
their dose in half to 2 and 1 half
milligrams for a woman if she's going to
go with a daily dosing protocol I would
suggest starting at about 2.5 Mig making
sure that she is reaping any benefits
but mitigating any potential side
effects uh from the drug and she could
titr trate as needed but I'm a big fan
of starting low and slow and making sure
that you don't have any uh detrimental
effects from any drug